Humane Borders records, 2000-2010 MS 471
University of Arizona
- Series I: Media Files, 2000-2010
  - Subseries 1: News clippings, June 1, 2000-December 29, 2009
    - Tucson Citizen, August 25, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Tucson Weekly, August 26, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 28, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 28, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - The Dallas Morning News, August 29, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Univision.com, August 30, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Lazos, August 30, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 30, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Mestizajel Immigration Information, September 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - U.S. Water News, September 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Tucson Weekly, September 2, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - KVOA, AZCentral.com, September 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - The Indianapolis Star, September 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - American Renaissance, September 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Quepasa, September 14, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Conafe, September 14, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Protestante Digital, September 14, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 17, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - The Arizona Republic, September 17, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - IBL News, September 18, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - The Arizona Republic, September 19, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 20, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 21, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Eyewitness News, KVOA 4, September 26, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 26, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Siskind’s Immigration Bulletin, September 27, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 29, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Theworld.com, October 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - ND.edu, October 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 212)
    - The Arizona Republic, October 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 213)
    - The World, October 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - MX Sin Fronteras, October 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - Agence Global, October 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - Oregonlive.com, October 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Protestante Digital, October 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Arizona Daily Sun, October 2, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - Arizona Daily Sun, October 2, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - Reuters, October 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 5, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - NRC Handelsblad, October 14, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - Jornada.unam.mx, October 30, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 30, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - The Associate, Franciscan Sisters, November 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Voznuestra.com, November 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - Newsday, November 6, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - Fundacion Mexico, November 13, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 21, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 22, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 2, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 6, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 235)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 15, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - White House Press Conference, December 20, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 238)
    - Tucson Weekly, December 23, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 239)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 25, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - NCTIMES San Diego and Riverside Counties, December 26, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 31, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 1, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 243)
    - GIS Tracks Earnings, January 1, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 244)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 1, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 245)
    - PCUSA, January 1, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - TCU Magazine, January 1, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 247)
    - KGUN 9 News, January 5, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - La Voz, January 5, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - South Florida Sun-Sentinel, January 9, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 250)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 10, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 13, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 14, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 14, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - Decaturdaily.com, January 15, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - Green Valley News, January 19, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - Reflection, January 23, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - Voice of America, January 28, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - El Independiente, February 1, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - The News Standard, February 4, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - Pinnaclepres.org, February 9, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - The Dallas Morning News, February 12, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - Fremont-Nebraska’s Community Newspaper, February 14, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - Rhode Island D.A. Quiroa e-mail, February 17, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - The Arizona Republic (Nexis.com), February 18, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 265)
    - Tucson Citizen, February 22, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 266)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 22, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 23, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 23, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - Radio Ondas, February 24, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - Tucson Citizen, February 26, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - Lefigaro International, March 1, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 2, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - Washington Post, March 7, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - Economist.com, March 10, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 13, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 16, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 16, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 18, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - Cox.net Tucson, March 21, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 22, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - LA Weekly, March 25, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - The Guardian (UK), March 27, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 283)
    - The Agonist, March 27, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 284)
    - Infoshop.org, March 27, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 285)
    - CBC.ca, March 27, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 286)
    - KVOA 4 Tucson, March 28, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 287)
    - Megatokyo, March 28, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 288)
    - BBC News, March 28, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 289)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 29, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 290)
    - Indymedia, March 29, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 291)
    - Arizona Indymedia, March 29, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 292)
    - Univision, March 29, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 293)
    - Desert Morning News, Salt Lake City, Utah, March 30, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 294)
    - News 5 Phoenix, March 30, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 295)
    - VivaTucson.com, March 30, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 296)
    - The Daily Illini University of Illinois, March 31, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 297)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 31, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 298)
    - The Washington Post, March 31, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 299)
    - Cox.net, March 31, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 300)
    - AZCentral.com, April 1, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 301)
    - KPHO.com News 5 - Phoenix, April 1, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 302)
    - New York Post, April 1, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 303)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 2, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 304)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 2, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 305)
    - Guardian.co.uk, April 2, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 306)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 2, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 307)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 3, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 308)
    - The Australian Christian, April 4, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 309)
    - Free Republic, April 4, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 310)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 4, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 311)
    - University of Texas, Austin, Texas, April 5, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 312)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 5, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 313)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 7, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 314)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 7, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 315)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 11, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 316)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 12, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 317)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 19, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 318)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 20, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 319)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 22, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 320)
    - LA Weekly, April 25, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 321)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 28, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 322)
    - Daily Northwestern, April 28, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 323)
    - Los Angeles Times, April 29, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 324)
    - Nogales International, April 29, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 325)
    - Washington Post, May 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Disciples World, May 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - KOLD News 13, May 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Loaves and Fishes, May 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - LA Times, May 2, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - The Telegraph, MaconTelegraph.com, May 3, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Arizona Republic, May 3, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Eyewitness News 4, May 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - AZCentral.com, May 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 6, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Kgun9.com, May 8, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - El Latino, May 9, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - The Arizona Republic, May 10, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Arizona Republic (email copy), May 10, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Terra.com, May 10, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - AZCentral.com, May 10, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Tucson Citizen (Map Correction), May 12, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 10, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 10, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 10, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - MSNBC, May 11, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Reuters, May 11, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Northwest Explorer, May 12, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - NCTimes.com, May 12, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - FoxNews.com, May 13, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 16, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - SignonSanDiego.com, May 23, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 23, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 24, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - The Nation, May 24, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Foxnews.com, May 24, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Huffingtonpost.com, May 24, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - The Arizona Republic, May 24, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - TucsonCitizen.com, May 24, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Eyewitness News 4, May 25, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - TucsonCitizen.com, May 26, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 26, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - NCM (New California Media), May 26, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - The New York Times, May 26, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - The New York Times, May 26, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 27, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - WSWS.org, May 27, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - The Arizona Republic, May 28, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - AZDdailysun.com, May 28, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - The Arizona Republic, May 28, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Washingtonpost.com, May 31, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - The United Methodist Church, June 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - The Tucson Citizen, June 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Seeds, June 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Intelligence Report - Southern Poverty Law Center, June 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - McCormick Seminary Alumni, Magazine, June 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - The Athens News, June 2, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Reporter Resources (United Methodist), June 3, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - American Beginnings, June 9, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 9, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - AZCentral.com, June 9, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 11, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 12, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - ABC Online, June 12, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Disciples World, June 13, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - NBC Nightly News, June 13, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 14, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 14, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 16, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 16, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 16, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 18, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - KOLD 13 News, June 18, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - United Press International, June 20, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Cox.net, June 20, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 22, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - University Baptist Church, June 26, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 29, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 29, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - KVOA, June 29, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - The Conservative Voice, June 29, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Thebta.org, June 30, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - AJUAA Magazine, July 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 4, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - DSApub.com, July 5, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 6, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 6, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 8, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - The Arizona Republic, July 10, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Spero News, July 11, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - KOLD News 13, July 14, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Arizona Republic, July 14, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 14, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 14, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 15, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 15, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 15, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Charlotte.com, July 15, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - The Arizona Republic, July 15, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - AZCentral.com, July 15, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - RenewAmerica.us, July 16, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 16, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 19, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - The New York Times, July 20, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Agape Press, July 20, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - WIStv.com, July 20, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 20, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 22, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 22, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 22, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 22, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 25, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 25, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 26, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 27, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 29, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 29, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 30, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Disciples World, August 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Arizona Capitol Times, August 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - The Seoul Times Co., August 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 2, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 4, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - KVOA 4, August 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Socialist Worker Online, August 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 6, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Leading the Charge, August 6, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Washington Post, August 6, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - The New Standard, August 7, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - KVOA 4 - Eyewitness News, August 10, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Tucson Weekly, August 11, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 14, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Chicago Tribune, August 17, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - The Washington Times, August 18, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - American Renaissance, August 18, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Voice of America, August 18, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Voices Magazine, August 19, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - USA Today, August 19, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - USA Today, August 19, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 20, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 24, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - The Washington Post, August 26, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 26, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Chicago Tribune, August 28, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - KVOA 4 Eyewitness News, August 29, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 30, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 30, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - United Methodist Communications, September 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - Democrats Abroad, September 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 2, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - People’s Weekly World, September 2, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - Sign On San Diego, September 4, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - AZCentral (AZ Republic), September 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Taipeitimes.com, September 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Jewish Times, September 6, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 7, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Arizona Jewish Post, September 9, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 10, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 14, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 16, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - SignOnSanDiego.com, September 22, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 23, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 23, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 24, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - KOLD News 13, September 25, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - La Estrella de Tucson, September 28, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Tucson Weekly, September 29, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - Monitor, October 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - National Journal, October 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - Los Angeles Times, October 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - Tucson Weekly, October 6, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 10, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Liberal Politics: US, October 17, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 18, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - SignOnSanDiego.com, October 18, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 18, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - The Arizona Republic, October 20, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - The Seoul Times, October 22, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 25, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 25, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 27, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 31, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Le Monde, November 8, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Surface Matters GIS Day Special, November 16, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 19, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 19, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - Chronicle, November 19, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 24, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 29, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 2, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 2, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Methodist Church, December 4, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 7, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 7, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 8, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - Detroit Free Press, December 8, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 8, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 8, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Tucson Weekly, December 8, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - AZWeekly, December 14, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - AZWeekly, December 15, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - San Antonio Express-News, December 15, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - San Antonio Express-News, December 15, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Washington Post, December 18, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Washington Post, December 18, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Dayton Beach News-Journal, December 19, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 28, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Journal of International Studies, January 1, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 1, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 4, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Bacon’s Multivision, January 11, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Denver Post, January 12, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 13, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Indie Wire: People, January 14, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Mysanantonio.com, January 15, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Cayman Net News, January 16, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - WashingtonPost.com, January 17, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 20, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - AZCentral.com, January 24, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - AZ Congress Watch, January 24, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - WashingtonPost.com, January 24, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Chronicle.com Houston, January 24, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Chronicle.com Houston, January 24, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - CNDH, January 24, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Billingsgazette.com, January 24, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - 1050 AM Federal News Radio, January 24, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - CNN.com, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - CNN.com, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Click2Houston.com, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - CNN.com, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Aljazeera.net, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Guardian Unlimited, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Herald Mexico News, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Excelsior, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Chronicle.com - Houston, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 26, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Turn to 23.com, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Diggers Realm, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - The Seattle Times, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - La Jornada, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - La Jornada, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - La Jornada, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - La Jornada, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - El Universal, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Newsmax.com, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - BBC News, January 25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 253)